{
    "id": "ddd68e75cccf4a89ac2d5a7e0fe2a4ff",
    "title": "Sentence Completion Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Don’t they teach any ………………………. at that school?",
            "description": "The plural manners means social behaviour.",
            "answers": [
                "manner",
                "manners",
                "mannerism"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Many are called but ………………………… are chosen.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "few",
                "fewer",
                "less",
                "little"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The old mariner had sailed the seas …………………………. 40 years.",
            "description": "We use for with duration.",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "since",
                "from"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………… are the true makers of history.",
            "description": "The masses means the common people.",
            "answers": [
                "Masses",
                "The masses",
                "The mass"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He showed a …………………………… grasp of the problem.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "masterful",
                "masterly",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Tie the package with a strong ……………………….",
            "description": "A cord is a rope or ropelike something.",
            "answers": [
                "cord",
                "chord"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "If you play a few ………………………….. on the guitar, I will sing along.",
            "description": "A chord is a string for a musical instrument or a combination of musical tones.",
            "answers": [
                "cords",
                "chords"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "With the ……………………….. of all the employees the work was done on time.",
            "description": "Cooperation means working together.",
            "answers": [
                "cooperation",
                "corporation"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I don’t believe in …………………………. punishment but I would love to give that boy a spanking.",
            "description": "Corporal means bodily or physical. Corporeal has a similar meaning but it is not used in this sense.",
            "answers": [
                "corporal",
                "corporeal"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The coroner was called to examine the …………………………",
            "description": "Corpse means dead body.",
            "answers": [
                "corpse",
                "corps"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The general’s decision to invade was a …………………………. mistake.",
            "description": "Costly is an adjective.",
            "answers": [
                "costy",
                "costly",
                "cost"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Is the witness’s story …………………………?",
            "description": "Credible means believable.",
            "answers": [
                "credible",
                "creditable"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}